# ATIYA HASSAN



atiya93hassan@gmail.com



(((

Urdu, English (read, write, speak)

## SKILLS

9 / 10 Effective Communication / Negotiation

8 / 10

Leadership 9 / 10

Risk Management

9 / 10

Critical Thinking & Problem Solving

9 / 10

## EDUCATION

BS (IT)

Shah Abdul Latif University Khairpur. 2017

#### References

To be furnished on Demand

# ABOUT ME

A highly motivated Software Engineer having more than 4 years of experience in Software Engineering applying for a job with your firm, I want to develop my analytical skills and knowledge in fast-paced environment. My career goal is to assume a role which allows me to take responsibility for the interpretation of commercial data for a well-respected and market-leading company.

# EXPERIENCE

#### **CS/IT Lecturer**

Halar Institute of Emerging Technologies (H-IET) 01/2020 – Present

• Supervision, instruction, training and orientation of student including demonstrating the proper use of a computer and software.

#### Assistant to Controller of Examination

SiSTech. / (Feb 2018 – Sep 2018)

- Establishing and maintaining internal controls
- Developed and implemented updates to existing applications.

#### Database Admin & CS/IT Lecturer

Dadabhoy Institute of Higher Education / (Feb 2017 – Feb 2018)

- Establish & Maintain student's record.
- Supervision, instruction, training and orientation of student.

### FINALYEARPROJECT

#### AGL—The Crawler Based Job Trend ANALYZER "Daryaft"

- Daryaft it is possible to know about the trending jobs in the market. The proposed system is a Web-based application where the user can view the trending jobs and technologies in the form of graphs and charts. This Crawler Based Job Trend Analyzer crawls the data from various sources and populates it in the database and then the analytical tools help to represent job trends in graphs and charts.
- Technologies used (Java, Rapid miner Studio and Server, JSoup, PHP, MySQL)

Data Collection and Data Analysis tools used for prediction of trends, ease to understand the results.